{"data":[{"question":"The French ___ a very polite people.","a":"is","b":"was","c":"are","d":"has been","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The + adj (The French, The old, the rich...): plays a plural noun which means a group of people who have common characteristics","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Ten years _________ a long time to wait.","a":"is","b":"were","c":"are","d":"have been","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Use a singular verb with sums of money or periods of time.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"A pair of trousers _________ hanging in the room.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"have been","d":"have","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A pair of trousers: the subject is \"a pair\" which is singular","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The number of casualties ___ unknown.","a":"have","b":"has","c":"are","d":"is","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The expression the number is followed by a singular verb while the expression a number is followed by a plural verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"My sisters as well as I ___ happy in those days.","a":"are","b":"were","c":"is","d":"was","answer":"2","explain":"\n - When the subject of a sentence is composed of two or more nouns or pronouns connected by \"and\/ as well as\", use a plural verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Bacon and eggs ___ his favorite breakfast.","a":"are","b":"were","c":"is","d":"have been","answer":"3","explain":"\n- \"Bacon and eggs\" is a dish - Singular verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Henry with his friends _________ on a trip to France.","a":"has left","b":"are left","c":"have left","d":"have been leaving","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Do not be misled by a phrase that comes between the subject and the verb. The verb agrees with the subject, not with a noun or pronoun in the phrase \n- The subject is \" Henry\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The United Nations ___ the old League of Nations.","a":"has been replaced","b":"have replaced","c":"have been replaced","d":"has replaced","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The United Nations is one organization- singular \n- This is not passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"A list of the names of all survivors ___ available.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"have","d":"has","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Do not be misled by a phrase that comes between the subject and the verb. The verb agrees with the subject, not with a noun or pronoun in the phrase \n- The subject is \" a list of \"- singular","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Early to bed and early to rise ___ a man healthy, wealthy, and wise.","a":"is made","b":"have made","c":"makes","d":"make","answer":"3","explain":"\n- \"Early to bed and early to rise\" is an action - Singular verb ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}